{
    "id": "1aef971cc1204bbe8ad208ae2b035e24",
    "title": "Gap Filling Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "Never ……………………. seen so much food.",
            "description": "When a sentence begins with a negative expression, the inverted word order is used. ",
            "answers": [
                "I have",
                "have I",
                "I saw"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "I look forward to …………………… from you.",
            "description": "The ing form is used after look forward to.",
            "answers": [
                "hear",
                "hearing",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "The faster you run, ………………………. you get tired.",
            "description": "In both clauses, we use the structure the + comparative + clause.",
            "answers": [
                "sooner",
                "the soon",
                "the sooner"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "………………….. our best efforts, we could not win the contract.",
            "description": "You can use despite or in spite of here. ",
            "answers": [
                "In spite of",
                "Inspite of",
                "Because of",
                "Despite of"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "It is time you ………………….. married.",
            "description": "The simple past is used with a present or future meaning after it is time. ",
            "answers": [
                "get",
                "have got",
                "got"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "I am extremely close to ………………………… friends I have.",
            "description": "The few means not many but all of them.",
            "answers": [
                "few",
                "the few"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Having …………………… the cats, she went to work.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "fed",
                "feed",
                "feeding"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "She speaks …………………………. she knows everything.",
            "description": "Either as if or as though is possible here. ",
            "answers": [
                "as",
                "as though",
                "as if"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "……………………….. I didn’t know his address, I couldn’t write to him.",
            "description": "As gives the reason so shows the effect. ",
            "answers": [
                "As",
                "So",
                "Because of"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "You …………………….. start spending more wisely.",
            "description": "Had better is used to give strong advice. ",
            "answers": [
                "have better",
                "are better",
                "had better"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "I would rather you ……………………. seeing her.",
            "description": "A simple past is used after would rather to refer to the present or future. ",
            "answers": [
                "stop",
                "stopped",
                "have stopped"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "He worked …………………….. hard that he fell ill.",
            "description": "Use so before an adjective and such before adjective + noun. ",
            "answers": [
                "such",
                "so"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        }
    ]
}